[
  {
    "question": "Wann begann der erste Kreuzzug?",
    "answera": "1096",
    "answerb": "1099",
    "answerc": "1080",
    "answerd": "1045",
    "type": "text",
    "rights": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "D/4",
    "answera": "D",
    "answerb": "E",
    "answerc": "F",
    "answerd": "F#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "x^2+x^2",
    "answera": "2x^2",
    "answerb": "x^4",
    "answerc": "x^8",
    "answerd": "2x^4",
    "type": "math",
    "rights": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "C/3",
    "answera": "C",
    "answerb": "F",
    "answerc": "C#",
    "answerd": "A",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 6
  },
  {
    "question": "A/4",
    "answera": "A",
    "answerb": "F",
    "answerc": "H",
    "answerd": "G#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "x^2*x^2",
    "answera": "x^4",
    "answerb": "x^2",
    "answerc": "2x^2",
    "answerd": "4x",
    "type": "math",
    "rights": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "E/5",
    "answera": "E",
    "answerb": "C",
    "answerc": "A#",
    "answerd": "H",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "D/4",
    "answera": "D",
    "answerb": "E",
    "answerc": "F",
    "answerd": "F#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "2x + 2x",
    "answera": "4x",
    "answerb": "x^2",
    "answerc": "2x^2",
    "answerd": "x",
    "type": "math",
    "rights": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "F/4",
    "answera": "F",
    "answerb": "D",
    "answerc": "E",
    "answerd": "G",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 5
  },
  {
    "question": "G/4",
    "answera": "G",
    "answerb": "E",
    "answerc": "F",
    "answerd": "F#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "B/4",
    "answera": "H",
    "answerb": "G",
    "answerc": "A",
    "answerd": "C#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Wann wurde Michael Jackson geboren?",
    "answera": "1958",
    "answerb": "1950",
    "answerc": "1980",
    "answerd": "1975",
    "type": "text",
    "rights": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "D#/4",
    "answera": "D#",
    "answerb": "E",
    "answerc": "F",
    "answerd": "F#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Was bedeutet Bird?",
    "answera": "Vogel",
    "answerb": "Welle",
    "answerc": "BÃ¼rde",
    "answerd": "Nichts, dieses Wort gibts nicht.",
    "type": "text",
    "rights": 1
  },

  {
    "question": "D/4",
    "answera": "D",
    "answerb": "E",
    "answerc": "F",
    "answerd": "F#",
    "type": "sheet",
    "rights": 4
  }
]
